<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sparsh Palkhiwala</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sparsh Palkhiwala</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 09:47:45 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NavAssist : The project that got me into Deep Learning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 09:47:45 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>Little Bit about NavAssist The YOLOv5 model has been meticulously fine-tuned and trained on a custom dataset comprising over 16,000 images, designed to capture Indian surroundings. This finetuned model achieves up to 70% precision in car detection and an overall precision of 65.4% for detecting all vehicles, all while maintaining real-time processing capabilities at 25 frames per second.&#xA;In addition, the model has undergone pruning to enhance resource efficiency, allowing it to run on lightweight devices such as the Jetson Nano.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resume/</guid>
      <description>About Me 🔭 I’m currently working on Speaker Diarization.&#xA;🌱 I’m currently learning about MongoDB, Graph VQA, Docker and Kafka.&#xA;📫 You can reach me via email at spalkhiw@asu.edu.&#xA;📄 Know about my experiences - Resume&#xA;⚡ Fun fact: I hold a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Electronics and Communication&#xA;Work Experience Machine Learning Intern @ Mirwork Inc | (June 2024 - Present) Engineered and optimized data extraction pipelines using YouTube API to process audio, gathering about 70+ hours of content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Sparsh Palkhiwala, a nerd running on coffee currently diving deep into the fascinating world of Speaker Diarization. My journey has taken me through bits of technology, from developing real-time vehicle detection systems to integrating AI for enhanced efficiency in research and writing processes.&#xA;Beyond the technical sphere, I am an melomane, a chess aficionado, and a dedicated gym-rat. These interests help me extreme some balance in the extremes of my life.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
